<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting started on INFINI Pizza</title><link>/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting started on INFINI Pizza</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installation</title><link>/docs/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>Installation # Pizza is compatible with all major operating systems. The package is compiled statically, and it does not require any external dependencies.
Automatic installation # Use the following command to automatically download the latest version of INFINI Pizza for your platform and extract it into /opt/pizza:
curl -sSL http://get.infini.cloud | bash -s -- -p pizza The optional parameters for the script are as follows:
-v &amp;lt;version number&amp;gt; (default is the latest version) -d &amp;lt;installation directory&amp;gt; (default is /opt/pizza) Manual installation # Visit the URL below to download the package for your operating system:</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>/docs/getting-started/configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/getting-started/configuration/</guid><description>Configuration # Pizza supports several methods to overwrite the default configuration.
Command lines # ➜ ./bin/pizza --help A Distributed Real-Time Search &amp;amp; AI-Native Innovation Engine. Usage: pizza [OPTIONS] [COMMAND] Commands: service Builtin service management (install, uninstall, start, stop) help Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s) Options: -l, --log &amp;lt;LEVEL&amp;gt; Set the logging level, options: trace,debug,info,warn,error --debug Run in debug mode, panic immediately with full stack trace -c, --config &amp;lt;FILE&amp;gt; -p, --pid &amp;lt;FILE&amp;gt; Place pid to this file -E, --override &amp;lt;KEY=VALUE&amp;gt; -h, --help Print help -V, --version Print version Configuration file # You can fully customize Pizza by utilizing the pizza.</description></item><item><title>Pizza CLI</title><link>/docs/getting-started/cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/getting-started/cli/</guid><description>Pizza CLI # The Pizza Command Line Interface (CLI) is a tool designed to facilitate quick and interactive communication with the Pizza server. It provides a convenient way for users to perform various tasks, such as querying data, managing configurations, and monitoring system status, directly from the command line.
Features # Interactive Querying # The Pizza CLI allows users to execute queries against the Pizza server interactively.</description></item></channel></rss>